The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
One celestial jade !?
Is he crazy !?
Who is he ?
How dare he humiliate the Whole Treasure Pavilion !?
He really made a bid...
But with such a price,
if we accept it,
the Whole Treasure Pavilion will lose face...
It would basically tell everyone that something's wrong.
But if we refuse,
it would go against the Ancestor's orders...
Brother Xu...
You're brilliant !
I'm impressed.
Alright !
In that case,
since fellow cultivator is the only bidder,
it's sold !
The grade 8 pill,
for one celestial jade
goes to...
Goes to this fellow cultivator !
It's sold !?
How could the pavilion agree to that ?
That's a grade 8 pseudo divine pill !
How could the Whole Treasure Pavilion treat this so casually !?
If fellow cultivator Sun has nothing else,
I shall take my leave.
What is it ?
In there
are over 50 000 celestial jades I've saved over the years.
There are also records of my alchemy
and artifact refining experiences.
I hoped that one day,
I might find an opportunity
to recover some of my cultivation.
Since I have no use for them anymore,
I'm giving them to you.
Life and Death...
Strength and weakness...
Kindness and resentment...
Cause and effect...
This old slave Sun Tai greets Master.
Karma...
Is this what comes after
the Life and Death Reincarnation Cycle Domain ?
This is the essence of Life and Death...
Yesterday was the cause
and today is the effect.
Sun Tai ended up here because of me
and also found peace because of me.
This
is karma.
Wasteland\NPlanet Ran Yun
Nearly 300 000 celestial jades
should be barely enough to breakthrough.
Formation...
activate !
Break !
Such might...
Is he warning us ?
I have enough celestial spiritual energy.
I only need enlightenment in my domain
to finish this breakthrough
and reach Middle stage Ascendant.
Since they insisted on dragging me into this matter,
then they must show me their goodwill.
My performance just now
should be enough for these three
to understand what's going on.
He had a breakthrough !
Let me test you !
Celestial guard...
go !
If he wanted to kill me,
that palm strike he used
would have already destroyed my body and soul.
What cultivation level does this person have ?
Peak Late stage Ascendant ?
Or perhaps...
even higher !?
So you are one of those that schemed to drag me down
in this matter.
Fellow...
Fellow cultivator Xu,
It... It was all my fault.
It's just that the Huan Family is too overbearing.
We were desperate
and resorted to this scheme.
I hope you understand.
I have no time for your excuses.
If you want my protection,
your sincerity
is far from enough.
What does fellow cultivator mean ?
I want 90% of your family's celestial jades.
You two
can come out as well.
Your Sun Family
will hand 70%.
As for you
Carefree Xanren, Zhao Chuanwen
will hand over 90%.
Moreover,
I want the remaining grade 8 pills you obtained 4 years ago
along with the belongings of that Huan Family member.
You must hand it over
without a single missing piece.
Finally,
if I still lack celestial jades for my cultivation in the future,
your three families
will be responsible for finding them for me.
If you can't do all this,
then you can pray for your lives.
These
are my conditions for protecting you.
Do you accept
or reject them ?
Fellow cultivator Xu,
the Sun Family accepts.
As long as we have your protection
and safely survive this calamity,
I'll give you myself
70% of our celestial jades.
Fine !
The Ran Family
also accepts.
We only hope you will keep your promise
and protect the Ran Family.
Brother Zhao,
we attacked together
in the ambush back then.
Don't think you can stay out of this !
Fellow cultivator Zhao,
we are all involved,
you can't escape this.
Forget it...
Then I
also agree.
My family is small,
these meager savings
are my entire wealth.
The Huan Family member's belongings are all in the bag.
Don't disturb me unless something important happens.
If the Huan Family comes,
I will act by myself.
This identity token is too plain...
Celestial guard,
test it.
There really is something wrong...
The material is ordinary
but there is a spell linked to the Life Soul inside it.
The Huan Family
is already aware this person is dead.
On Planet Yun Xia,
I discovered a vein
of flame metal.
An entire vein of flame metal !
The Heaven Defying Bead is only missing the metal element
to be complete and recognize me as its Master.
Sun Xi,
engrave a map of planets you know in the Allheaven Star System onto a jade slip
and send it to me immediately.
Planet Yun Xia...
Found it !
This flame metal vein
is mine !
Fellow cultivator Xu,
are you leaving Planet Ran Yun ?
I trust you.
But this matter
is a matter of life or death for us.
The Huan Family's threat is imminent.
I will not go back
on what I have promised.
They're here !
The Huan Family really came !
I am a rank 2 guard of the Huan Family of Planet Thousand Illusions,
Huan Dong.
Ascendant cultivators of Planet Ran Yun,
come to pay your respects.
Scram !
You're courting death !
Who are you !?
How dare you interfere with the Huan Family's affairs ?
You're unworthy
of knowing my name.
Death Finger !
Condense !
What kind of lightning is this !?
This person is definitely not Middle stage Ascendant !
Fleeing ?
I must escape
and report to my lady !
With your strength
you dare to oppose my Huan Family !?
If you don't release me,
you will die for sure !
The Huan Family's vengeance is inevitable.
We can't resist it...
Fortunately, Xu Mu is here.
Fellow cultivator Huan,
what business do you have on our Planet Ran Yun ?
What business ?
Ran Family Ancestor,
you should know very well !
So you really are the ones that killed
my Huan Family member.
Ran Xuefeng,
Sun Xi,
Zhao Chuanwen !
The bloodlines of your three families
have come to an end !
Fellow cultivator Xu,
will you
let us handle this person ?
Fellow cultivator Xu,
my Huan Family Ancestor is back !
How dare you act like this ?
You surely don't think that you can oppose the Ancestor
with your Ascendant cultivation ?
What's the cultivation level
of the Huan Family Ancestor ?
The Ancestor's cultivation has reached the second step.
Several thousand years ago, he was already at the Illusory Yin and Corporeal Yang realms.
You can handle this person.
It has nothing to do with me.
I have important matters,
I'll be leaving now.
I'm the personal guard of Miss Huan Mei.
My lady
is the core disciple the Ancestor brought back from the Alliance !
If you harm me,
Miss Huan Mei will never let you off !
Huan Mei !?
What was her original name ?
If you spare me,
I will tell you.
Soul Search !
Liu Mei...
This woman really gained a great fortune
by coming to this Allheaven Star System.
Fellow cultivator Xu,
now that Huan Dong is dead,
the Huan Family will surely investigate !
I will come back
in 3 months.
The Soul Lamp of Huan Dong has gone out.
He is dead.
The location of his death
is Planet Ran Yun.
Please give the order, Ancestor.
Send forces to Planet Ran Yun !
Destroy the planet,
extinguish their bloodlines !
Planet Ran Yun
is a small place.
Destroying it
is as easy as flipping my hand.
However,
Huan Dong
is one of Huan Mei's underlings.
This vengeance
should be personally carried out by her.
Understood.
The Ancestor is wise
but Miss Huan Mei's blood exchange ritual is not yet...
Then finish it early !
After the blood exchange ritual is complete,
let Huan Mei
personally handle this matter.
As the Ancestor orders !
Issue the order,
from now on
no one can leave Planet Ran Yun !
Set up the Star Sealing Grand Formation.
Allow entry but not exit.
Not even an ant
is allowed to escape from me !
Planet Yun Xia
Sun Tai pondered for a long time before standing up. He looked out the window and softly said, “You… Can you promise me something?”\NWang Lin didn’t open his eyes and calmly said, “Speak.”\N\N“If you really send me off in 20 years, please take my ashes back to the Alliance Star System’s planet Dark Moon. There is a mountain that pierces into the sky. I remember there being a village at the foot of the mountain. Please send my ashes back there.”\NWang Lin let out a sigh, then he opened his eyes and nodded at Sun Tai.\N\NSun Tai revealed a smile of gratitude. At this moment, he was like a mortal old man who wanted to return to his roots after he died and not become a foreign ghost.\NHe took out a bag of holding, slowly put it down, and said, “Here are some celestial jades. I been saving them for the day when I recover my cultivation, but after seeing you, I feel like I don’t need them anymore. There are also records of my alchemy and artifact refining experiences. Take them as my thanks for sending his old man home.”\N\NGiving away his bag of holding was him loosening a knot in his heart. It meant that he had given up on recovering and had given up on everything, including the unwillingness he felt for the hundreds of years he had spent here.\NIt was because of Wang Lin that he ended up with such a fate, but also because of Wang Lin that he was relieved of the pain in his soul for hundreds of years. If there was karma, this was it.\N\NThe sun setted and Wang Lin closed his eyes. Life and death, karmatic cause and karmatic effect are only separated by just one thought, much like Yin and Yang, true and false.\NThis was the way the world was.\N“Karma is the path after the Life and Death Domain. It can be said that karma is the root of life and death; it is because there is a karmatic cause of life that there is a karmatic effect of life.” Wang Lin felt a hint of enlightenment, but everything still felt foreign. It was as if he could see it but not touch it.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.